<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food</string>

    <string name="email_hint">Email here</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Password here</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="testlongstring">You can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the textYou can spell check very long text areas without compromising any performance hits. Regardless of the size of the text, UltimateSpell only sends small portions of the text to the server as needed, while the user spell checks through the text</string>


</resources>
